{
    "subject": "resource/Dave_Davies",
    "predicate": "ontology/associatedBand",
    "object": "resource/The_Kinks",
    "human_readable": "Dave Davies is associated with The Kinks.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9023825526237488,
            "question": "Who is Dave Davies associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7635008096694946,
            "question": "Who are some other famous members of The Kinks besides Dave Davies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39055371284484863,
            "question": "What musical instrument did Dave Davies play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32907477021217346,
            "question": "Name some famous songs by The Kinks."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31566789746284485,
            "question": "Where was The Kinks originally formed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3149087429046631,
            "question": "What band is Dave Davies known for being a part of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2600227892398834,
            "question": "Is Dave Davies famous for his work in rock music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25113457441329956,
            "question": "What genre of music is The Kinks known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22060231864452362,
            "question": "What made The Kinks stand out from other bands of their time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11409693956375122,
            "question": "What decade was The Kinks most popular?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Dave Davies is associated with The Kinks.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8380_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What made The Kinks stand out from other bands of their time?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8380_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of music is The Kinks known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8380_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Dave Davies famous for his work in rock music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8380_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8380_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8380_129.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8380_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8380_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8380_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8380_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8380_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8380_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8380_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8380_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide multiple references to Dave Davies being the co-founder and lead guitarist of The Kinks, thus supporting the statement that Dave Davies is associated with The Kinks."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}